Finding Aid for the Katherine Philips Edson Papers LSC.0235
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence (1913-1932)
  - (1925), 42 pieces
    - Mollie Ray Carroll., Minimum wage decisions, Justice Stone, Hiram Johnson, child labor and Wadsworth-Garrett proposed constitutional amendments, prohibition, National Consumers League, Robert La Follette. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - (telegram) Hiram Johnson. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Hiram Johnson., National Consumers League, National League of Women Voters, opposition to timing of minimum wage amendment, Wadsworth-Garrett amendment, Washington Conference of Women in Industry, Father John A. Ryan, Meyer Lissner. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - (telegram) Hiram Johnson., Federal minimum wage amendment. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Belle Sherwin., Federal minimum wage amendment. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - (1926), 22 pieces
    - Hiram Johnson., Proposed constitutional amendments, Belle Sherwin, Mollie Ray Carroll, Dr. Mariana Bertola. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Florence Prag Kahn., Proposed constitutional amendments, National Woman's Party, League of Women Voters, Federation of Women's Clubs, Women's Trade Union League, California Legislature, prohibition. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Dr. Mariana Bertola., Minimum wage and other proposed constitutional amendments, Hiram Johnson, League of Women Voters, League of Nations, Katherine Philips Edson and women's organizations. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Henry M. Robinson., Industrial Welfare Commission studies. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Burnita S. Matthews., California labor regulations for women: night work, 8-hour day, feminist objections.; Biographical sketch of Katherine Philips Edson for League of Women Voters convention. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Florence Prag Kahn., Industrial Welfare Commission, women and night work, state blanket legislation vs. commission regulation. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - H. Robert Braden., Industrial Welfare Commission working conditions and publicity. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - A.G. Arnoll., Industrial Welfare Commission and canning industry, lack of cooperation from Southern California canners. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - (1927), 7 pieces
    - Florence Kelley., Industrial Welfare Commission, Friend Richardson reappointment of Katherine Philips Edson, new governor, Clement C. Young; A.B.C. Dohrmann, Walter Mathewson, new Industrial Welfare Commission commissioners: James W. Cos(telegram)lo, George F. Neal, Syndicalism Act, Chester Rowell, Ulysses S. Webb, John McGilvray, federal labor legislation. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Mary S. Gibson., 8-hour law, National Woman's Party, Walter G. Mathewson. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - A. Laurie Brazee., Edson family. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - John B. andrews., Social health insurance, League of Women Voters, Industrial Welfare Commission enforcement of regulations. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - (1928), 56 pieces
    - Sidney Hillman., California Conference of Social Agencies program. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Daisy Lee Worcester., Social Agencies Conference, Sidney Hillman. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Reverend Robert E. Lucey., Conference, Sidney Hillman, unemployment and minority groups. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Louise Drury., California Conference of Social Agencies, children in California industry. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Louise Drury., Conference, Chester Rowell, Dr. Langley Porter, social health insurance, unemployment. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Louise Drury., Conference, Dr. Haven Emerson, Paul Eliel, Edgar Perry, Paul Scharrenberg. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Hiram Johnson., Fletcher Dobyns, Long Beach radio station, Ventura Valley flood, William Mulholland. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Edgar R. Perry., Industrial Welfare Commission investigations. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Louise Drury., Conference program, W.S. Goodrich, Dean Willard Hotchkiss, Will J. French, unemployment. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Louise Drury., Social Work Conference program. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Hiram Johnson., Asking for support of Jones bill to alleviate unemployment in construction. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Warren McBryde., Conference program. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Edgar R. Perry., Conference program, Dean Willard Hotchkiss, Sidney Hillman, Daisy Lee Worcester, Frederick J. Koster, Paul Scharrenberg. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Frederick J. Koster. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - William Kimsey. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Chester Rowell., Conference program, discrimination against Asian-Americans in California, Herbert Hoover. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Hiram Johnson., Senator Reed Smoot. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Dean Willard E. Hotchkiss., Conference program. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - A.B.C. Dohrmann., Industrial Welfare Commission investigation of wages and hours in California banks, reluctance of Bank of Italy, W.W. Douglass, James A. Bacigalupi, Alexander Heron, Will J. French. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Anita Eldridge., Pan-Pacific Women's Conference, Elisabeth Christman, Sidney Hillman, U.S. Supreme Court, Frances Seibert, Muriel Hagney, Paul Scharrenberg. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Marion J. Harron. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Marion J. Harron., Supreme Court minimum wage decisions, Justice George Sutherland, William Reed Powell, prohibition, minimum wage administration in Washington, D.C., and in California, details of union fight against Industrial Welfare Commission and Katherine Philips Edson in 1921-22 when Industrial Welfare Commission wanted to lower minimum wage, A.B.C. Dohrmann, Walter Mathewson. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Florence Kelley., Industrial Welfare Commission, Richard Cushing. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - ? (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Ethel E. Osborne--Ford., Pan-Pacific Women's Conference. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - (1929-31), 27 pieces
    - Mrs. L.C. Weeks., Katherine Philips Edson's resignation from Daughters of the American Revolution. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Elisabeth Christman., Minimum wage in glove-making industry, Zonta club, Ethel Smith, California court decisions on Industrial Welfare Commission and overtime, raise in age of female minors to 21. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Samuel Leask., Position for Leask on Commission for Study of Public Education, Franklin Hichborn. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Clement C. Young., Recommendation of Samuel Leask. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Hiram Johnson., Mrs. Sullivan on Industrial Welfare Commission, Will J. French, Herron, Lyman King. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Clement C. Young., Protective legislation for women. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Mrs. A.E. Neuenberg., Endorsing Governor Clement C. Young for reelection. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alexander B. Stewart H.L. Carnahan., Canning industry and Industrial Welfare Commission, Longmoor, wages, hours, working conditions. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - H.L. Carnahan., Canning industry, Alexander B. Stewart's letter. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Mrs. A.E. Neuenberg. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Hiram Johnson. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Hiram Johnson., James Rolph, Jr., Marshall Hale, Mark Requa, Louis Mayer, Ida R. Koverman, Woman's Republican Club, A.B.C. Dohrmann, Fred Dohrmann, Ben F. Schlesinger, Women's Christian Temperance Union. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Theodore Roche., Clement C. Young, James Rolph, Jr., Katherine Philips Edson's Industrial Welfare Commission position, depression, Edson family. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - W.A. Johnstone., State Civil Service and Industrial Welfare Commission employees. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - (1932), 22 pieces
    - Mabel Kinney., Industrial Welfare Commission, Rolland Vandegrift. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - ?, Industrial Welfare Commission and Labor Bureau, labor unions, Paul Scharrenberg, andrew Furesette, Taxpayers Association, Mabel Kinney's changes in Industrial Welfare Commission.; Proposed merger of Industrial Welfare Commission with Division of Labor Statistics and Law Enforcement. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Mabel Kinney., James Rolph, Jr., Rolland Vandegrift, Industrial Welfare Commission. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. Barnum and League of Women Voters Executive Council., Industrial Welfare Commission, State Federation of Labor, Mabel Kinney's methods, James Rolph, Jr., canning industry, Rolland Vandegrift, consolidation of Industrial Welfare Commission with Bureau of Labor Statistics. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt., Recommending Frances Perkins for Secretary of Labor, congratulating Roosevelt on his election. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - California legislature., Industrial Welfare Commission history, Franklin D. Roosevelt, Governor Lehman, urging that Industrial Welfare Commission not be consolidated with other state agencies, Nellie Pearce, Governor Friend Richardson's administration. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - A.B.C. Dohrmann., Industrial Welfare Commission, Rolland Vandegrift, Paul Scharrenberg, Mabel Kinney, Taxpayers League, League of Women Voters. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. Buwalda., Industrial Welfare Commission consolidation, Paul Scharrenberg, Labor Bureau, andrew Furesetti, Taxpayers Association, Mabel Kinney. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - (UNDATED), 7 pieces
    - ?, Florence Kelley, Industrial Welfare Commission, Sam Clover. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Carrie C. Catt., Woman suffrage in California. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Mary Dewson., Industrial Welfare Commission, canning industry. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Mary Dewson., Industrial Welfare Commission, canning industry, National Recovery Act. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Maud Wood Park. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Correspondence (1909-1920)
  Letters to Katherine Philips Edson and Various Persons, from:
  - (1909), 6 pieces
    - William P. James., Divorce law. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Caroline Severance., Edson family. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Amos Fries., West Point, ideal of equality of opportunity. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Florence Kelley., Speaking engagement before the Friday Morning Club. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - (1911-1912), 32 pieces
    - ?, Edson family, London, Lloyd George. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - C. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - John D. Works., Owen health bill, Professor Irving Fisher, medical legislation, California Federation of Women's Clubs. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Mary Roberts Coolidge., Women in California government, Civic League. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff., California woman suffrage, Meyer Lissner, California elections. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Witter Bynner (?). (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Meyer Lissner., Political conditions in Los Angeles, Lissner's plans. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff., Los Angeles convention of National Municipal League.; Reprint from Los Angeles Tribune criticizing film shown to children on germ theory of disease. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Hollis J. Backus., Referring to above clipping, deploring film, American Medical Association, Christian Science. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff., Katherine Philips Edson candidate for National Municipal Council. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Meyer Lissner. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - John Ihlder., Poor housing construction in Los Angeles. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. Overton G. Ellis., California trip, Dr. and Mrs. T.J.J. See. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Delos F. Wilcox. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff., National Municipal League. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff., National Municipal League, Mrs. Blankenship, Ohio. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Harris Weinstock., California labor and minimum wage. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Florence Kelley., Katherine Philips Edson's appointment to California Bureau of Labor Statistics, National Consumer's League, short work-day cases, minimum wage, Sidney Webb, Massachusetts law, Ohio constitutional amendment. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - (1913), 26 pieces
    - Mrs. James Orr., Setbacks, Oregon health measure, Red Light measure in California. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Hiram Johnson. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Louise Carey Smith., Recommending 8-hour day for fruit packers. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - W. Wright for Keir Hardie, British House of Commons., Acknowledging letter, referring Katherine Philips Edson to article by Philip Snowden. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Meyer Lissner., Election campaign, municipal conference, Edward A. Dickson, Willis I. Morrison. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Meyer Lissner., Progressive Party, Democratic Party, health certificate bill, Willis I. Morrison, campaign. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - C.T.(?) Wolcott., Albert E. Boynton, Mrs. Porter. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. James Orr. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Nettie H. Hicks. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Meyer Lissner. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - (telegram) Hiram Johnson., Health certificate bill. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - (telegram) Hiram Johnson., Health certificate bill, Snow. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Chester Rowell., Health certificate bill, Hiram Johnson. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - (telegram) Hiram Johnson., Health certificate bill. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. James Orr., Health certificate bill, Hiram Johnson. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - William D. Stephens. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. James Orr., Katherine Philips Edson's article, state Civil Service Commission. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Chester Rowell., Miss Todd, Girls' Training School Board appointment, Hiram Johnson and suffrage, Francis Heney and campaign, Kent, John D. Spreckels, Crane, Rowell as candidate, Edward A. Dickson, Los Angeles County requirements for U.S. senator, Rowell's position in Southern California and San Francisco. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - (September-December 1913), 39 pieces
    - Jessie Hardy Stubbs., Annie Bock's anti-suffrage propaganda. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hiram Johnson., Mr. and Mrs. Fremont Older, Miss Todd, Harris Weinstock, Chester Rowell, Minimum Wage Commission, Walter G. Mathewson, Dr. James McBride. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Chester Rowell., Girls' Training School Board, Marshall Stimson. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hiram Johnson., Appointments to the school board. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Ben F. Schlesinger., Minimum Wage Commission, Walter G. Mathewson. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hiram Johnson., Judge Frank J. Murasky, Industrial Welfare Commission. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Ben F. Schlesinger. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Dr. James McBride., Minimum wage, Hiram Johnson, Industrial Welfare Commission. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. Hugh M. Hill., Article on Katherine Philips Edson by Peter Clark Macfarlane, desire to help obtain woman suffrage. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Peter Clark Macfarlane., Congratulations on Industrial Welfare Commission appointment, Hiram Johnson, Theodore Roosevelt. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - George Creel., Asking for information on woman suffrage, article on commercialized papers. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Walter G. Mathewson., Peter Clark Macfarlane's article on Katherine Philips Edson, laundry workers' wage, engineers' wage. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff., Article on Katherine Philips Edson. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - John Francis Neylan., Article on Katherine Philips Edson, Peter Clark Macfarlane. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Walter G. Mathewson., Recommending Henry Murgotten for Industrial Welfare Commission. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hiram Johnson. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Walter G. Mathewson., Talbott, minimum wage legislation, A.B.C. Dohrmann, Progressive Party, Hiram Johnson. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Edith M. Thomas. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Harris Weinstock., (telegram)ling Katherine Philips Edson not to worry over political situation. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Walter G. Mathewson., Wages for Industrial Welfare Commission employees, A.B.C. Dohrmann, advocating equal wages and suffrage for women, Hiram Johnson, John Eshleman. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Walter G. Mathewson., Judge Frank J. Murasky, asking Katherine Philips Edson to speak to United Labor Club to register members as Progressives. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hiram Johnson., Appointments to Girls' Training School Board, Mrs. Stephens. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Meyer Lissner. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Chester Rowell., Speculations on gentlemanliness, its social causes and possible effects.; English women's questionnaire on woman suffrage and answers from Katherine Philips Edson (?). (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - (January-June 1914), 76 pieces
    - Hiram Johnson., Girls' Training School Board. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hiram Johnson., Dr. Adelaide Brown, Dr. Glaser, State Board of Health appointment, Miss Michelson, State Board of Prison Directors' appointment. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - (telegram) Hiram Johnson., Voter registration of Progressives. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Edith M. Thomas. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hiram Johnson., Miss Michelson, Edwin T. Earl, Edward A. Dickson, State Board of Health appointment, Dr. Sherwin Gibbons, Dr. Adelaide Brown, Dr. Glaser, Progressive registration. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chester Rowell., Burnett Sanitarium evasion of 8-hour law, correspondence-course graduation for nurses. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chester Rowell. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Walter Mathewson., Progressive registration. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chester Rowell., Rowell vs. Francis Heney for nomination for senate, Democratic registration in Taft (California), Earl newspapers, Meyer Lissner; Democratic senate candidate, James D. Phelan; Raker, Theodore Bell, Griffin, workmen's compensation, Hiram Johnson. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Walter Mathewson., Minimum wage, Samuel Gompers, labor unions and employees and Industrial Welfare Commission, Florence Marshall, employers' attitude toward apprentices. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Walter Mathewson., 8-hour initiative measure. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Walter Mathewson., Civic Center Dinner, Dr. Parker, Durst, Paul Scharrenberg. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Alexander McCabe., Hiram Johnson's reception in Southern California. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hiram Johnson., Tense Sacramento situation. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Robert LaFollette., 8-hour law in California. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - John P. McLaughlin., Squabbling in Labor Bureau's southern office, Ben F. Schlesinger and Johnson campaign, Katherine Philips Edson's illness. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hiram Johnson., Katherine Philips Edson's illness, milk bills, A.W. Frye. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Florence Kelley., Miss Wald and 8-hour day for nurses, Miss Dock, apprentice wages. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Clinton R. Woodruff., California Progressive-Republican split, Meyer Lissner, National Municipal League. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chester Rowell., Samuel Shortridge, John D. Spreckels, Edwin T. Earl and his papers, Edward A. Dickson, opposition to labor element among Progressives, Rowell's campaigning in Northern California. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hiram Johnson., Government employees and political activity. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chester Rowell., Earl papers and senatorial race, Edward A. Dickson, Hiram Johnson and gubernatorial campaign, John D. Fredericks. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Martin C. Madsen. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Walter Mathewson., Industrial Welfare Commission, Harry Scheel, Albert Bonnheim, Abe Ruef, Hiram Johnson, California Republican convention, Jay O. Hayes. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chester Rowell--Meyer Lissner., Election campaign, labor and Progressive registration. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - James S. Roche. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - John Francis Neylan., Girls' Training School. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Miss D.F. Thayer., Appreciation for Katherine Philips Edson's talk before Gilroy Women's Civic Club. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - George P. West., Federal Industrial Relations Commission planning California investigation, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Frank P. Walsh, Major Boughton, Bouck White, Upton Sinclair, conservatism lessening in East, John Gavit, Woodrow Wilson, John Reed, William Allen White, Paul Scharrenberg, Harris Weinstock, John R. Commons, Harrison Gray Otis, Harry Chandler, Hiram Johnson. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Walter Mathewson., News clippings on Jay O. Hayes' renunciation of Republican candidacy for governor in favor of John D. Fredericks, the Olders, Albert Bonnheim, Industrial Welfare Commission and civil service. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chester Rowell., Edward A. Dickson, Judge Willis I. Morrison, Edwin T. Earl, Meyer Lissner, Rowell-Heney campaign, Harrison Gray Otis, Miss Todd, Jane Addams. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Meyer Lissner. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Walter Mathewson., Joseph D. Radford, Tom Monahan, Red and Black Hayes' Church, Harris Weinstock, Albert Bonnheim, Chester Rowell' speaking engagement. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - State Board of Control--Industrial Welfare Commission., Expense accounts. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - (July-December 1914), 92 pieces
    - Walter Mathewson., Francis Heney, Francis Keesling, canning industry working conditions, Joe Kelly of Bureau of Labor Statistics, Paul Scharrenberg. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Mrs. James Orr-- Mrs. Palmer., Red light abatement, Franklin Hichborn. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - To the Editor, Los Angeles Express and Los Angeles Tribune., Publicity for Chester Rowell. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Hiram Johnson., John D. Fredericks, woman suffrage and Johnson and Woodrow Wilson, Los Angeles Times. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Belle Harris Ellis., List of Progressive women in Riverside. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walter G. Mathewson., Harry Scheel, A.B.C. Dohrmann, Hiram Johnson and labor. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - San Diego County Federation of Women's Clubs., List of Progressive women. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Mrs. James Orr., California Federation of Women's Clubs activities. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Freddie M. Mitchell., List of Progressive women in Bakersfield. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Martha McCan. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walter Mathewson., Clipping describing desire of Eastern women to move to Washington on hearing of high minimum wage, effect of this argument on workers. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walter Mathewson., Harry Scheel, Miss C.F. Kett's report for Industrial Welfare Commission, garment industry of San Francisco--working conditions. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walter Mathewson., Election campaigning. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Frank P. Walsh., U.S. Industrial Relations Commission hearings in California. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walter Mathewson., Election campaigning. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Robert Telfer-- Walter Mathewson., Election campaigning. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Robert Telfer-- Walter Mathewson., Campaigning. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walter Mathewson., Campaigning. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - (telegram) Carrie C. Catt., Inviting Katherine Philips Edson to go East to help campaign there. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - (telegram) Carrie C. Catt. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ben Schlesinger., Labor unions and minimum wage. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Clara Schlingheyde., Katherine Philips Edson's campaigning in East, Carrie C. Catt. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Harriet B. Odgers. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walter Mathewson., Industrial Welfare Commission, canning industry, Harry Pyle, State Federation of Labor convention, Sarah Hagan. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Gertrude Beeks-- Ben F. Schlesinger., Labor unions and minimum wage in California. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Gertrude Beeks-- Ben F. Schlesinger. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - (?)-- Harry Scheel., Industrial Welfare Commission, Harry Pyle, canning industry. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walter Mathewson-- Helen Bary. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ben F. Schlesinger. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ben F. Schlesinger-- Gertrude Beeks., Minimum wage, state enforcement, union labor. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - H...B... -- Ben F. Schlesinger. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Chester Rowell., Katherine Philips Edson's trip East. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Carrie C. Catt., Campaign situation in East. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Hiram Johnson., Thanks for congratulations on election victory. (Box 2, Folder 6)